<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/</link><description>Dhaka Observer</description><language>en</language><atom:link href="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/application/views/frontend/feeds/dhaka_observer.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Salahuddin Ahmeds wife seeks prime ministers intervention</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6206&amp;&amp;cat_id=2</link><description><![CDATA[She went to the Prime Ministers Office (PMO) on Thursday to seek Sheikh Hasinas appointment. I have come to request the prime minister to take steps to find my husband. Shes also a mother, a wife, like me and she will understand my pain, Hasina Ahmed]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6206</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4553.jpg"/></item><item><title>Salman always be important part of my life | Katrina</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6205&amp;&amp;cat_id=28</link><description><![CDATA[Once romantically linked with him, actress Katrina Kaif is all praise for Salman Khan and says her journey in life and Bollywood would have been difficult without the unique superstar.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6205</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4552.jpg"/></item><item><title>Bapparaj debut movie Kartuz running successfully</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6204&amp;&amp;cat_id=7</link><description><![CDATA[As a film director, Bapparaj debut movie Kartuz running successfully. The film has been released in over 60 cinema halls across the country on March 6. The film Kartuz also features late director Chashi Nazrul Islam in the cast.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6204</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/45511.jpg"/></item><item><title>Stocks fell for the 6th straight session</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6203&amp;&amp;cat_id=26</link><description><![CDATA[Stocks fell for the 6th straight session yesterday, as the countrys economic outlook remained weak with the prolonged political turmoil.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6203</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4550.jpg"/></item><item><title>UK Bangladeshis at higher risk of poverty: Report</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6202&amp;&amp;cat_id=12</link><description><![CDATA[British people of Pakistani and Bangladeshi origin are around three times more likely to be in poverty compared to their white counterparts while people of Indian descent have largely closed that gap, according to new research by Oxford University.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6202</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4549.jpg"/></item><item><title>Umpire continues to play for India</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6201&amp;&amp;cat_id=6</link><description><![CDATA[Mahmudullah Riad was batting to rebuild the Bangladesh innings after quick dismissal of the opener Tamim Iqbal and Imrul Kayes in the 7th over when the Tigers score reached 33-2.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6201</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4548.jpg"/></item><item><title>Govt bends to IMF pressure on new VAT law implementation </title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6200&amp;&amp;cat_id=5</link><description><![CDATA[The government has finally agreed to a proposal of the International Monetary Fund on implementing the new value added tax, much to the worry for both consumers and small and medium businesses.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6200</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4547.jpg"/></item><item><title>PM Hasina vows tough punishment for arsonists</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6199&amp;&amp;cat_id=1</link><description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina said tough punishment would be given to those BNP-Jamaat men resorting to militant acts in Bangladesh and killing people by arson and bomb attacks in the name of blockade and hartal.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6199</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4545.jpg"/></item><item><title>Solar aeroplane heads to Myanmar</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6198&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[Solar Impulse is on its way from Varanasi in India to Mandalay in Myanmar (Burma). The solar-powered plane is currently flying the fourth leg in its historic bid to fly around the world powered only by the Sun's rays.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6198</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4544.jpg"/></item><item><title>82 Shibir men held with huge firearms, bullets in Chittagong</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6197&amp;&amp;cat_id=1</link><description><![CDATA[Detectives in an overnight drive arrested 82 activists of Jamaat-e-Islami and its student wing Islami Chhatra Shibir along with huge firearms and bullets from Chittagong Government College and Hazi Mohammad Mohsin College in the city early Wednesday.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6197</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4543.jpg"/></item><item><title>Have we been sleepwalking into a networked nightmare?</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6196&amp;&amp;cat_id=8</link><description><![CDATA[Our long-held vision of an Internet of Things is here. Ours is an age of an all-encompassing network - from connected cars to lampposts. Should we have taken more care with what we wish for?]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6196</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/45421.jpg"/></item><item><title>Deadly clashes in Yemen close Aden airport</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6195&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[Gunmen opposed to President Abed Rabbo Mansour Hadi have attacked the international airport in Aden, exchanging fire with security forces. Hadi had declared the southern city the nation's provisional capital. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6195</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/45411.jpg"/></item><item><title>Maturity test for Brazil&apos;s democracy</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6194&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[A wave of protests in Brazil puts President Dilma Rousseff under increasing pressure. Radical opponents of the government want an impeachment, but they have had little response. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6194</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4539.jpg"/></item><item><title>Swedish police blame gang feud for deadly pub shooting</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6193&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[A shooting in a Swedish bar left at least two people dead and more than a dozen wounded. Police say two men burst into the crowded eatery in Goteborg and opened fire with automatic weapons. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6193</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4538.jpg"/></item><item><title>No sign of take off as Lufthansa pilots extend strike to three days</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6192&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[Lufthansa passengers are set to face a third consecutive day of travel chaos after German pilots union Vereinigung Cockpit extended the ongoing strike until Friday. The walk-out is the thirteenth in a year. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6192</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4537.jpg"/></item><item><title>US Fed keeps markets guessing about rate hike</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6191&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve has opened the door even further to a June interest rate hike. But it said it will need to see 'further' improvement in the job market before acting, warning that growth had 'moderated somewhat.' ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6191</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4536.jpg"/></item><item><title>Great Barrier Reef region braces for Cyclone Nathan</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6190&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[Northeastern Australia has battened down the hatches as it prepares for a strong cyclone forecast to hit coastal areas north of Cairns. Tropical Cyclone Nathan first threatened the coast last week. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6190</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4535.jpg"/></item><item><title>Hart masterclass thwarts marvellous Messi but Catalans progress</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6189&amp;&amp;cat_id=6</link><description><![CDATA[A superb performance from Lionel Messi inspired Barcelona to a 1-0 victory over Manchester City in their last-16 second leg tie at Camp Nou on Wednesday, as the Spanish giants ran out 3-1 winners on aggregate.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6189</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4534.jpg"/></item><item><title>City corporation polls in Dhaka, Chittagong on April 28</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6188&amp;&amp;cat_id=1</link><description><![CDATA[The Election Commission on Wednesday announced schedule for mayoral elections to two major Bangladeshi cities -Dhaka and Chittagong fixing April 28 for voting.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6188</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4533.jpg"/></item><item><title>Newly weds be mused: enjoy free train ride</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6187&amp;&amp;cat_id=1</link><description><![CDATA[Railway minister Mujibul Haque has declared that newly weds will get free ride on train to any destination. To take the opportunity the newly weds have to come to Kamlapur Railway station, where they will be provided with free tickets for any destina]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6187</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/45321.jpg"/></item><item><title>Remove billboards or face actions, says CEC </title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6186&amp;&amp;cat_id=1</link><description><![CDATA[Chief Election Commissioner Kazi Rakibuddin Ahmad has asked the aspirants in elections to Dhaka and Chittagong city corporations to strictly maintain code of conduct of city polls.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6186</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/45311.jpg"/></item><item><title>Khaleda asks Hasina to return Salahuddin to his family </title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6185&amp;&amp;cat_id=2</link><description><![CDATA[Bangladesh Nationalist Party chief Khaleda Zia on Tuesday asked Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina either to return missing BNP leader Salahuddin Ahmed to his family or produce before the court without any delay.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6185</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4530.jpg"/></item><item><title>Bangladeshs biggest challenge  bowl out worlds best batsmen</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6184&amp;&amp;cat_id=6</link><description><![CDATA[India possess the best batting lineup in world cricket and Bangladeshs bowlers will confront their biggest challenge in the World Cup quarter-final, skipper Mashrafe Mortaza said Wednesday.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6184</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/44631.jpg"/></item><item><title>Salahuddins wife plans to knock PMs door</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6183&amp;&amp;cat_id=1</link><description><![CDATA[Hasina Ahmed, the worried wife of BNP joint secretary general Salahuddin Ahmed who remained missing since March 10 night, on Tuesday said she will seek Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina s intervention to find out her husband.]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6183</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4529.jpg"/></item><item><title>Violence as ECB protest begins in Frankfurt</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6182&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[Violence has marred the start of anti-austerity rallies in Frankfurt, held to coincide with the European Central Bank (ECB) opening its new headquarters. Police are expecting around 10,000 protesters to demonstrate. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6182</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4528.jpg"/></item><item><title>Aid continues to arrive in cyclone&#45;stricken Vanuatu</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6181&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[Relief workers have been working to deliver aid to the cyclone-stricken islands of Vanuatu. Villagers, particularly on the outer islands, have been in desperate need of food and water since Saturday. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6181</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4527.jpg"/></item><item><title>China pressures South Korea over US missile system</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6180&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[Beijing calls on Seoul not to permit the US to deploy advanced anti-ballistic missile system, but analysts say China's demand is merely the latest attempt to prise South Korea out of Washington's sphere of influence. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6180</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4525.jpg"/></item><item><title>AirAsia plane search ended with bodies still missing</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6179&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[Indonesia is set to end the search for passengers still missing after an AirAsia jet crashed into the Java Sea late December. While more than a hundred bodies have been recovered, dozens are unaccounted for. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6179</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4524.jpg"/></item><item><title>Seven accused triggermen from Srebrenica massacre arrested</title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6178&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[Prosecutors from Serbia and Bosnia have arrested former militiamen accused of carrying out killings during the 1995 Srebrenica massacre in Bosnia. The mass killings were the worst on European soil since World War II. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6178</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/4523.jpg"/></item><item><title>Lufthansa strike cancels hundreds of flights </title><link>http://dhakaobserver.com/english/index/news_details_facebook?id=6177&amp;&amp;cat_id=3</link><description><![CDATA[German's flagship air carrier Lufthansa has canceled hundreds of flights after pilots began a two-day walkout on Wednesday. And more cancelations are expected as the two sides remain divided. ]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">6177</guid><media:thumbnail width="92" height="52" url="http://dhakaobserver.com/english/uploads/images/news/45221.jpg"/></item></channel></rss>